Cinderella
Cinderella's sister
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 13
Now the one with the spring water.
Before you tell her, I'm going to end it all by telling her.
If I tell them first, you'll fail.
Unburdened, I can simply wait for her disposition.
You or Gi Jeong... this is the way to make sure none of you can get Dae Seong True Winemakers.
I didn't know it before.
Eun Jo...
Open the door.
Open the door, Eun Jo.
Eun Jo!
Eun Jo! Open the door!
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear,  ♫
♫ I can't bear it so I can't laugh. ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
Eun Jo! Eun Jo!
Eun Jo!
Open the door! Eun Jo!
♫ but even if I bite my lips and bear it
♫
♫ You are the only one who is my person ♫
♫ I am living day after day ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear again,  ♫
♫ I can't bear it so I can't laugh. ♫
Hey.
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
Why is he like that?
You should go in. He's drunk.
Are you drunk, too?
Jeong Woo...
If you're not sleeping, come out.
What is it? Why?
Drink this and go to bed.
Give him some, too.
Noona.
Let me ask you something.
What do you like about him?
What?
Why? Why do you like him?
Stop saying useless things.
Don't go.
Do you not like him?
Are you giving him honey water because he's drunk when you don't even like him?
With two cups, so you can use me as an excuse?
You...
I told you not to mess around.
Did I tell you or not?
What do you think you're doing?
Let go!
Let go...
It hurts.
Do you want to die?
Hey.
Let go of me.
What do you think you're doing?
Eun Jo.
What's wrong? Are you drunk?
I have something to say to you.
I have to tell you first.
Yes, please do so. Go inside and do so.
Eun Jo.
I have something to say to you.
Before my older brother swallowed it up,
I wanted to get it first.
After I took it, I was going to
give it back to your dad straight away.
Your dad...
passed away because of me.
He collapsed when he heard me talking to my older brother on the phone.
Before Chairman Hong Han Seok of Hong Joo Ga came to you,
I wanted to tell you first.
Let go.
Girl, you want me to kill you?
Jeong Woo, why are you so mad?
Why do you like that guy?
What's so great about him? Do you know that guy... Do you know who he really is?
Do you know it and yet you like him?
He may look like a goody two shoes but he is really a two-faced son of a bi*ch. Forget him.
Be careful
with what you say.
What did you say?
Don't
speak carelessly.
What are you?
What do you know?
Don't be like that.
Jeong Woo.
That person,
is someone who even if I don't look at him, it's painful;
Even if I see him it's painful;
If he's there, it's painful;
if he's not there, it's painful;
When he looks at me and smiles, it's painful,
When he smiles at anyone, it's painful.
When he calls
my name, its painful,
When he doesn't call it, it's painful.
Unless I drop off the face of the earth
all of a sudden,
I think I will continue to suffer, Jeong Woo.
Even so, it's better having him.
If I can see his face and hate him...
That is,
better than
not having that person.
Kiddo, you counsel even Noona's self-pity.
You grew up a lot, our Jeong Woo.
You're awake?
Let's talk a bit.
I said lets's talk a bit!
So, the stuff I heard last night,
don't speak a word of it to Noona.
I said don't do it. Why aren't you replying?
I have to.
What did you say? You will? You'll say it?!
You don't realize that it's one thing if she finds out about it by herself,
but to hear it from you, straight from your mouth is another thing. You shouldn't do that to Noona.
I will do it.
I have to do it. Move out of the way.
If you say it, Eun Jo won't be able to breathe.
So you can feel at ease, you'll spit out everything inside you?
To Noona? Then what about her? What will happen to her then?
She'll find out somehow and I can't let her hear it from someone else.
You keep your mouth shut too.
I have to do it. I have to do it myself!
Are you going to kill Eun Jo?!
If you tell her, you're not the only one who's going to die.
Eun Jo is also going to die along with you.
Shut your mouth.
She says it's painful whether she sees you or she doesn't, but that its better to see you and suffer.
She says it's better to see you! This person.
You committed a crime, right?
You want to receive punishment.
Then accept your punishment of not being able to speak of your wrongdoing for the rest of your life,
so you won't ever receive forgiveness for it.
Just try telling her and you'll see.
Trying to confess,
you just try opening your mouth before Eun Jo.
She says it's painful whether she sees you or she doesn't,
but that its better to see you and suffer.
She says it's better to see you!
Oppa.
Where have you been since this morning?
Is Eun Jo at home?
No, she went out.
Where? Where did she go?
Did she go to the winery? To the factory?
She went to the lab.
Oppa!
Have a safe trip.
MMM
- Hello.
- Where are you now?
I'm on my way somewhere. Why?
Where?
Why?
Where are you going?
There's one lab machine that broke down so I sent it in for repair.
Because I didn't want to wait, I'm on the way to finding it.
What's wrong?
Eun Jo, I have something to tell you in a hurry.
Say it.
Will you come?
Can you not tell me over the phone?
I can't. I'd like it if you came right now.
I'll go wait at home.
Okay.
Hello.
Where are you?
I have to go home. Right now, Hyo Seon-
I'm at your school right now. From here to where you are...
Tell me the quickest way to get to you.
I have to say it now.
If I don't say it now, I might not ever be able to.
That rascal told me not to tell you, but I want to tell you, Eun Jo.
I have to say it.
What are you saying?
Where are you? Tell me quickly.
♫  and waited for you  ♫
♫  Even my memory which turned away  ♫
♫  doesn't know that I longed for you  ♫
♫  Looking only in this direction  ♫
It's me, Father. Just listen to me.
I don't want to hear your response.
I've been thinking deeply about why I accepted your offer in the first place.
I thought it was because I despised Hyung Gi Jeong, and despised the rest of the family who were so mean to my mom.
So, I thought I'd take revenge as much as I could. That's all I thought.
♫  Will you who knows everything about me  ♫
But, that was a lie.
I guess my true intention was to put my name in the family registry
and become a proud member of Hong Distillery.
I'm definitely sure that was it.
But Father, I'm throwing it all away now.
Father, you take it all.
My shares, my house.
I don't know how much there is but I will give them all to you.
I'll also give up being your son.
I'm telling you I'll put everything on the line, Father.
After this time, if you come to me or even a little bit closer
to Dae Seong True Winemakers where I am now,
since I am already not your son,
things that might seem depraved to others...
such as a son ratting out his father and older brother to the media
and reporting the brother to the police for what he did to Dae Seong True Winemakers...
You're going to see all those things happen.
Yes, you can call me crazy.
I am on my way to see the girl who says it's better to see me even if she suffers.
I am going to repent and then...
However, I don't know whether I can still keep staying there or watch over her...
But, I'm going to ask her those things.
If only that kid gives me permission, I'll do that.
Father, stay healthy.
♫  If I can always look at you  ♫
♫  The day I return to your side again will come again  ♫
What did you say?
Just, I was in a hurry.
Gi Hoon was looking for you,
and it didn't seem like he was searching for you about work.
And that it was for a reason I didn't know...
That scared me.
And I didn't like it.
I'm also embarrassed of myself to death.
But, that was bigger than my embarrassment.
What could it be?
What could it be that Gi Hoon was searching for you so urgently.
With such an earnest expression on his face...
Because of those thoughts, I lost my mind.
Despite my humiliation.
I'm confessing to you.
Let's go together.
Come with me.
If your heart is that unstable, stay by my side.
I'm really embarrassed, Eun Jo.
Dae Seong True Winemakers' Unfiltered Wine
Gi Hoon, just this once.
Just this once, let me meet her.
Please set it up for me and then I'll do the rest.
She's the only woman I really fell in love with at first sight.
Do you know what it's like to fall in love at first sight?
Just answer your phone.
Huh? Oh okay.
I'll listen to your words well.
Hello?
Pardon? Yes?
What is she saying? Yes?
Yes. Why?
What's wrong with Dad?
What?
Ah, so why would my dad collapse?!
Did you call Dad?
What are you saying?
They're saying that after talking to you on the phone,
dad went to the bathroom and collapsed.
What?
A makgeolli tasting contest?
Yes. The two of you guys are definitely experts without question.
You must participate not matter what.
Explain what you're saying in more detail.
I'll send you the details later over mail.
I'm going to cover a story now. You guys can do your own business or
Whether you drink here or not, do whatever you want.
Eun Jo, was he originally like that?
Isn't he a bit strange?
Kim Dong Soo.
I have something to tell you.
Can you look into something for me?
What happened to us... that Japanese export scam...
Can you look into who did that?
It's a relief that he survived this.
I almost couldn't make the time to even come like this.
Gi Tae, you go back and rest too.
Stop there.
You almost couldn't even make this time?
Can you say something like that in this situation?
Are you praising yourself that you made the time and came when you are too busy to even make the time?
Lower your voice.
Who was the one who made Dad faint?
Well, I don't know.
Who was it because of?
Do you think I wouldn't know?
You and Mom, day in and day out putting your heads together and plotting to oust dad from Hong Distillery...
Do you think I wouldn't know?!
Lower your voice. You're in front of a patient.
A patient?
Is Dad
just a patient to you?
Why is a loud noise coming from a hospital room?
I don't need it all. You're all like beggars.
We need to meet with Lawyer Kim.
Let's hold off for now.
We can't prepare for a lawsuit while he's lying down here.
There could be negative rumors.
I wanted to wrap this up before the next shareholder's meeting.
If it goes wrong again, how much longer do we have to wait?
If we take any action as soon as he recovers, it won't look good either.
Let's stop everything for the time being, Mother.
I thought I told you not to let anyone get in here.
First, since Lawyer Kim is waiting let's go and meet him.
We have to listen to what he has to say.
Father.
What is this?
Is this how you lived your life? Until now?
What is it?
Someone came.
Someone came and he's here asking to see the madam of the house.
That person... What did he do?
He said his relative sister called Song Kang Sook lives in this house
and she is filthy rich. Just one word from him and she'll bring him money.
He played quite a bit.
We're holding onto a wrist of his and he's asking for some money.
Your younger sibling.
I understand. I understand, so go.
Go, quickly.
I'll take care of it myself, so go quickly.
Eun Jo.
Among Mom's relatives is there anyone named Jang Taek Geun?
What did you say?
So, what will you do?
What would I do? It's nothing, so don't worry about it.
It's nothing?
You're saying it's nothing? This is nothing?
I'll take care of it myself.
What will you do if Hyo Seon becomes suspicious?
What will you do if Hyo Seon finds out?
How would she know? I'll take care of it myself so you-
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do about it?
I filled the tub for you. Wash before it gets cold.
- Hyo Seon.
- Yeah?
Mom's condition is a bit off and she's not feeling well right now.
You're not going to like it if you go in there.
Okay.
Is Mom sick?
She's not hurt, she's just a bit off.
There's something you need to do.
We can't lease the Japanese equipment soon enough but that person...
Your call is being directed to the voice mail box.
That person... I haven't been able to get in touch with him all day.
You try calling him.
Your call could not be connected.
Jeong Woo.
Jeong Woo!
Okay, I'll go.
As soon as you get up in the morning.
That's right. Don't worry.
If we don't give them the money, they'll keep coming back.
I said don't worry. I'll resolve it, just believe me.
I won't allow him even show his face before your house.
Don't worry.
No,
I'll go with you.
Let's do that.
Why would you go somewhere like that? I said just believe me.
I...
I will meet Ajusshi Jang because I want to talk to him.
Sleep early.
Eun Jo.
Something is wrong, right?
What's wrong?
No.
Make some noise, girl. You almost scared me to death.
Give me all the money those people askd for.
Are you crazy? Why would I give you that money?
You can't let them keep coming back here!
He can sue me for all I care.
You want to make a scene and alert all the elders of the family?
Get the money ready.
Goo Dae Seong
A person came into my life.
Like the spring breeze.
There is a scent of flowers in the spring breeze.
Like being echanted by the floral breeze, I became enchanted by that person.
I swore to massage her swollen feet forever.
How would you know that!
I have too many vows. That's how a foolish man is.
This foolish man makes another vow.
To make sure there are no tears in that woman's eyes.
Oppa.
Oppa, where have you been?
You didn't even pick up your phone all day.
Was something wrong?
What's wrong?
Oppa.
Why are you like this?
You didn't say anything to Eun Jo, did you?
Did you?
Is that the most important thing?
That I'm part of the Hong Joo Ga family...
The reason why I came to this house...
What I did to Ahjussi...
You do know all that but,
Eun Jo's welfare is the only thing that matters to you.
And as long as Eun Jo is safe,
it's okay for you to share a room with someone like me?
Would it be okay?
But, ... why are you letting me off?
I thought you said you were going to give it back.
I believe those words.
Do you believe them?
If I don't, then I'll feel too bad for Noona who likes you.
Even though I can't understand at all
why on earth she likes someone like you.
Mr. Hong! Testing equipment...
Hi, Mr. Hong! I'm Dakai Miura. This is confirmation that the testing equipment you requested is ready to be leased.
We will have the equipment shipped to you by air as soon as possible. Thank you. Good luck...
The equipment issue is resolved.
Now, all Eun Jo has to do is to run her tests. Go find Eun Jo.
Okay, she said she'd come at night.
Is that so?
Get up. Let's go to buy rice.
Gu Eun Jo Interview
Honest Business! "Dae Seong True Winemakers"
Ahjussi, if you just this once, give us rice under the same conditions
when President Goo Dae Seong was around,
we will never forget your kindness.
Why are you sitting turned around?
Look at me, please?
The consumers of our rice wine insist that only eco-friendly rice in Gyeonggi-do should be used as raw material.
I believe this could be the chance for your rice to gain world-wide fame.
Ahjussi.
I know you came to my dad's funeral secretly.
Why did you just leave without letting me know?
But if I had seen you there, I probably would have cried until I passed out
thinking of Dad.
I'm really thankful
that you came and said farewell.
Ahjussi.
Eat up.
Okay, I'll eat.
I'll do everything as you say.
Gi Hoon...
you're not going to go anywhere, are you?
Then, that's fine.
I'm growing every day,
and if you stay by my side and not go anywhere,
I'll also become a cool kid like Eun Jo.
I come on to you too strongly, don't I?
I won't do that.
I said I won't do that.
You're a very good person, Hyo Seon.
Nobody among us approaches a person with sincerity like you, knocks on their heart
or moves them. Except you.
Why are you being like this?
Since you're complimenting me, I'm afraid there'll be a twist.
I'm scared.
I'm so envious of your good qualities.
You're a good person. Believe that.
You said I knocked on your heart.
But, why aren't you touched?
I was touched.
The fact that you liked me, believed in me,
I know your sincerity.
You know?
It's because I know that I'm saying this.
It's because I know that I'm also rejecting you like this.
Like right now.
What?
I'll be loyal to the two of you.
No matter how the future turns out, what frightening things it brings,
even if I receive an unforgiving punishment all my life, I will bear it.
What does that mean?
Thank you for your feelings, and sorry that I couldn't accept them.
Is it because of Eun Jo?
No.
You're going to reject Eun Jo too?
I got rejected by Eun Jo.
So, right now, I got rejected by you, right?
That's right.
Officially, right?
That's right, officially.
Nothing I'm holding onto...
I really have nothing stable.
Eun Jo, Mom,
and even you.
You're standing well by yourself.
A little wobbly perhaps. But you are going well.
Stay well, Hyo Seonn. You're growing up very well.
Follow me.
Ahjussi.
Eat slowly. No one's going to take it from you.
But, who did you say you were?
Just eat.
Jeong Woo, just stay standing there.
Get in.
Okay.
I said get in.
Eun Jo!
If by any chance I don't come back to pick you up after two or three hours, find your way home by yourself.
What did you say-? What are you doing right now?
Eun Jo, Eun Jo!
Why are you like this?
Get off.
Why are you telling me to get off?
I said get off!
Please save me, Mister.
Save me.
I feel like I might die.
I feel like I'm going to die every day.
I'm barely surviving.
I'm living because I can't die.
If you add your burden on top of mine...
I...
I..
I'm my mom's daughter, mister.
Song Kang Sook's daughter, Eun Jo.
Cold-hearted bitch...
Eun Jo.
When you were drunk and slept,
there were times when I just wanted to kill you.
You didn't know that, did you, Mister?
I really even held a knife up.
When you were drunk,
and you laid a hand on my mom.
This hand.
This hand...
I was going to cut it off, I wielded a knife.
That young brat who was only 10 or so,
to cut his hand off...
I had such ugly thoughts everyday.
Did you know?
If I were to live having such nightmares again,
it's better not to live at all, Ahjussi.
I'm being sincere.
Eun Jo, I was wrong-
Shut your mouth, Ahjussi.
You're not supposed to say you did wrong.
If you did wrong, then you should never do that again.
But even though you did wrong, you did it again!
Even though you said you did wrong now, next time too...
you'll do the same mistake again.
Ahjussi, watch me.
How your wrong-doing can easily kill a person...
I'll show you.
Young girl!
Young girl.
- Young girl.
- Let go of me!
Let go! Let go!
Let go of me!
I'm going to kill myself.
Let go! I'm going to die!
A lacking man that I am... I helplessly look on while she's reeling.
That person's repeated lies are all a disgrace to me.
When that person sometimes goes to meet her old man from before then comes back home and smiles at me,
emotions of anger, despair, and sadness
take turns in overcoming me.
I'd like to ask that person why does she that,
but this foolish man is too scared to open his mouth that can't even say a word.
The moment I open my mouth to speak,
The life I've been living with that woman for the past 8 years
will become a lie and disappear.
The fact that my life will continue without her in it,
That's what I'm most afraid of.
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
Can't you give up everything?
I won't do that.
I was rejected.
I feel like my heart is ripping, Unni.
Noona, are you okay?
Move aside!
♫  My bruised heart  ♫
What will happen if I stab you in the back and reveal who you are?
I won't leave him be.
I'm just not going to let him do this.
♫  Wherever you are  ♫
♫  Can't you hear my voice?  ♫